<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ImmuniCare</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="forward"><![CDATA[->]]></string>
    <string name="back"><![CDATA[<-]]></string>
    <string name="immuni">Immuni</string>
    <string name="care">Care</string>
    <string name="wait">Wait for 24 hours for us to \n validate your account</string>
    <string name="ty">Thank you!</string>
    <string name="back_login">Go back to login</string>
    <string name="validate_here">Validate here!</string>
    <string name="not_yet_connected">Not yet connected?</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="be_informed">Be informed about vaccination schedule \n and other important information.</string>
    <string name="welcome_back">Welcome back!</string>
    <string name="parent">Parent</string>
    <string name="good_day">Good day!</string>
    <string name="next_appointment">Next Appointment</string>
    <string name="latest_announcement">Latest Announcement</string>
    <string name="new_article">New Article</string>
    <string name="menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="child_s_profile">Child\'s Profile</string>
    <string name="immunization_record">Immunization Record</string>
    <string name="articles">Articles</string>
    <string name="calendar">Calendar</string>
    <string name="concern">Concern</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="add_your_child_s_image">Add your child\'s image</string>
    <string name="enter_child_s_name">Enter Child\'s Name</string>
    <string name="birth_date">Birth Date</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="place_of_birth">Place of Birth</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="mother_s_name">Mother\'s Name</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="barangay">Barangay</string>
    <string name="kg">kg</string>
    <string name="cm">cm</string>
    <string name="height">Height</string>
    <string name="father_s_name">Father\'s Name</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="add_child_info">
        If you wish to edit your child information
        go here and you can also
        add more child information</string>
    <string name="child_info">Add child info</string>
    <string name="barangay_389">Barangay 389</string>
    <string name="hepatitis_b_vaccine">Hepatitis B Vaccine</string>
    <string name="bcg_vaccine">BCG Vaccine</string>
    <string name="pentavalent_vaccine">Pentavalent Vaccine \n (DPT-Hep B-HIB)</string>
    <string name="pneumococcal_conjugate">Pneumococcal Conjugate \n Vaccine (PCV)</string>
    <string name="inactivated_polio">Inactivated Polio \n Vaccine (IPV)</string>
    <string name="meassles_mumps_rubella">Meassles, Mumps, Rubella \n Vaccine (MMR)</string>
    <string name="at_birth">At Birth</string>

    <string name="bcg_txt1"><![CDATA[The dose of BCG is 0.05 ml for children < 12 months and 0.1 ml for children ≥ 12 months]]></string>
    <string name="bcg_txt2">Given at the earliest possible age after birth preferably within the first 2 months of life</string>
    <string name="bcg_txt3"><![CDATA[For healthy infants and children > 2 months who are not given BCG at birth, PPD prior to BCG vaccination is not necessary. However, PPD is recommended prior to BCG vaccination if any of the following is present:]]></string>
    <string name="bcg_txt4">Congenital TB</string>
    <string name="bcg_txt5">History of close contact to known or suspected infectious cases</string>
    <string name="bcg_txt6">Clinical findings suggestive of TB and/or chest x-ray suggestive of TB</string>
    <string name="bcg_txt7">In the presence of any of these conditions, an induration of 5 mm is considered positive and BCG is no longer recommended</string>

    <string name="hep_txt1">Given intramuscularly (IM)</string>
    <string name="hep_txt2">Administer the first dose of covalent HBV to all newborns ≥2kgs within 24 hours of life </string>
    <string name="hep_txt4">The final dose is administered not earlier than 24 weeks of age </string>
    <string name="hep_txt3">A second dose is given 1–2 months after the birth dose </string>
    <string name="hep_txt5">Another dose is needed if the last dose was given at age &lt; 24 weeks </string>
    <string name="hep_txt6">Administer HBV* and HBIG (0.5ml) within 12 hours of life. HBIG should be administered not later than 7 days of age, if not immediately available. </string>
    <string name="hep_txt7">With birth weight ≥2 kgs, administer HBV within 12 hours of birth and determine the mother’s HBsAg as soon as possible. If HBsAg (+), administer HBIG not later than 7 days of age.</string>
    <string name="hep_txt8">With birth weight &lt; 2 kgs, administer HBIG in addition to HBV* within 12 hours of life</string>
    <string name="hep_txt9">For infants born &lt;2 kgs, the 1st dose received at birth is not counted as part of the vaccine series. Additional 3 HBV doses are needed</string>

    <string name="dpt_txt1">Given intramuscularly (IM)</string>
    <string name="dpt_txt2">Given at a minimum age of 6 weeks. </string>
    <string name="dpt_txt3">The primary series consists of 3 doses with a minimum interval of 4 weeks </string>
    <string name="dpt_txt4">Booster series consists of 3 doses until adolescence with the following schedule: </string>
    <string name="dpt_txt5">2–23 months (DTP) </string>
    <string name="dpt_txt6">4–7 years (DTP) </string>
    <string name="dpt_txt7">9–15 years (Td/Tdap)  </string>

    <string name="opv_txt1">The Oral Polio Vaccine is available as part of the government’s National Immunization Program </string>
    <string name="opv_txt2">The primary series consists of 3 doses beginning at age 6 weeks with a minimum interval of ≥4 weeks IPV </string>
    <string name="opv_txt3">The first dose of IPV is given together with the third dose of OPV </string>
    <string name="opv_txt4">The second dose of IPV is given together with the measles vaccine at 9 months</string>
    <string name="hep_2">For infants born to HBsAg (+) mothers (preterm or term infants):</string>
    <string name="hep_3">For infants born to mothers with unknown HBsAg status:</string>

    <string name="dpt_1">DIPHTHERIA, TETANUS, PERTUSSIS VACCINE (DTP)</string>
    <string name="dpt_2">Ideally, the minimum interval between booster doses should be at least 4 years</string>
    <string name="dpt_3">Full-dose DTP should preferably be used only until age 7 years, but package inserts should be consulted for maximum age indications of specific products</string>
    <string name="settings_txt1">In this settings, you can set the reminder, notifications, date</string>
    <string name="reminder">Reminder</string>
    <string name="notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="notification_txt1">In this notification, you can turn on your\nnotification so that it can appear on your\ntop of your phone or on your lock screen\nfor the admin\'s announcement, etc</string>

    <string name="terms_and_conditions">
    Welcome to ImmuniCare! By using the ImmuniCare mobile application, you agree to the following terms and conditions. Please read them carefully.\n
 \n   <b>1. Acceptance of Terms    </b>
 \n\nBy downloading, installing, or using the Application, you agree to comply with and be bound by these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use the Application. Your continued use constitutes your ongoing agreement.
\n
  \n  <b>2. User Eligibility    </b>
  \n\nThe Application is intended for use by residents of Barangay 389, Philippines, specifically parents, guardians, health workers, and barangay administrators. Users must be 18 years or older to create an account or access certain features. Minors may use the Application under the supervision of a parent or guardian, who assumes responsibility for their actions.
\n
   \n <b>3. User Accounts   </b>
  \n\nUsers are required to provide accurate and complete information during registration. Providing false or misleading information is prohibited.
  You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account credentials. Sharing your credentials with others is strictly forbidden.
        \n\nYou agree to notify us immediately if you suspect unauthorized access to your account. ImmuniCare is not liable for damages resulting from unauthorized access caused by your failure to secure your credentials.
\n
        \n  <b>4. Use of the Application</b>
   \n\nThe Application is designed for the following purposes:
   \n\n• Managing and viewing child immunization schedules and records.
   \n• Receiving vaccination reminders and health-related notifications.
   \n• Accessing educational materials about immunizations.
   \n• Facilitating communication with barangay health workers and administrators.
   \n\nUsers agree to use the Application solely for its intended purposes and not to:
   \n\n• Violate any applicable laws or regulations.
    \n• Engage in unauthorized access, distribution, or modification of the Application’s data or features.
    \n• Transmit harmful, malicious, or offensive content.
   \n• Reverse engineer, decompile, or otherwise attempt to derive the source code of the Application.
\n
   \n <b>5. Privacy Policy    </b>
   \n\nYour use of the Application is also governed by our Privacy Policy, which explains how we collect, use, and protect your personal information. By using the Application, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy. We do not share personal information with unauthorized third parties.
\n
    \n<b> 6. Data Accuracy and Responsibility   </b>
   \n\nUsers are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of the data they provide. ImmuniCare is not responsible for errors arising from incorrect or incomplete information entered by users. Misuse or falsification of data may result in account suspension or termination.
\n
   \n <b>7. Limitation of Liability    </b>
   \n\nImmuniCare is provided "as is" without warranties of any kind, either express or implied. To the fullest extent permitted by law, we disclaim liability for any direct, indirect, incidental, or consequential damages, including but not limited to:
    \n\n• Failure to follow vaccination schedules.
    \n• Misuse of the Application.
    \n• Technical issues, interruptions, or data breaches beyond our control. Users agree to use the Application at their own risk.
\n
   \n <b>8. Intellectual Property    </b>
   \n\nAll content, features, and functionalities of the Application, including logos, graphics, and software, are the intellectual property of ImmuniCare or its licensors. Users may not copy, distribute, or modify any part of the Application without prior written consent. Any unauthorized use of the Application’s content may result in legal action.
\n
  \n  <b>9. Modifications to Terms    </b>
  \n\nWe reserve the right to update or modify these Terms and Conditions at any time. Changes will be effective upon posting in the Application. Continued use of the Application signifies your acceptance of the updated terms. Users are encouraged to review the terms periodically.
\n
  \n  <b>10. Termination    </b>
  \n\nImmuniCare may terminate or suspend your access to the Application for violations of these Terms and Conditions or any applicable laws. Users may terminate their account by contacting our support team. Upon termination, all access to the Application and its features will cease immediately. ImmuniCare reserves the right to retain anonymized data for legal and research purposes.
\n
   \n <b>11. Governing Law    </b>
   \n\nThese Terms and Conditions are governed by the laws of the Philippines. Any disputes arising from these terms will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in Manila, Philippines. Users agree to resolve disputes through good faith discussions before seeking legal recourse.
\n
  \n <b>12. Contact Information    </b>
  \n\nFor questions, feedback, or concerns, please contact us at:
  \n\n  • Email: Marvyjimenez970@gmail.com
   \n • Facebook: Barangay 389 Zone 40
\n
   \nBy using the ImmuniCare Application, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agreed to these Terms and Conditions.
\n
  \n  <b>Effective Date: January 2025    </b>
</string>
</resources>